question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
